<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieCatalogueUIUX</string>
    <string name="tab_movies">MOVIES</string>
    <string name="tab_tv_shows">TV SHOWS</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>

    <array name="data_movie_name">
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>BumbleBell</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>Once Upon A Deadpool</item>
        <item>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item>The Movie DragonBall Broly</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_movie_date">
        <item>October 3, 2018</item>
        <item>December 7, 2018</item>
        <item>April 25, 2018</item>
        <item>December 13, 2018</item>
        <item>October 24, 2018</item>
        <item>December 15, 2018</item>
        <item>November 21, 2018</item>
        <item>December 11, 2018</item>
        <item>January 3, 2019</item>
        <item>March 6,1993</item>
        <item>January 16, 2019</item>
        <item>October 19, 2018</item>
        <item>November 27, 2018</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_movie_score">
        <item>Score : 75%</item>
        <item>Score : 68%</item>
        <item>Score : 83%</item>
        <item>Score : 73%</item>
        <item>Score : 81%</item>
        <item>Score : 65%</item>
        <item>Score : 67%</item>
        <item>Score : 69%</item>
        <item>Score : 76%</item>
        <item>Score : 73%</item>
        <item>Score : 65%</item>
        <item>Score : 63%</item>
        <item>Score : 60%</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_movie_overview">
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers and falls in love with struggling artist
            Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer until Jack
            coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side
            of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own
            internal demons.
        </item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater
            kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans
            to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way
            is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
        </item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too
            large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows:
            Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity
            Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all
            of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate
            of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a
            survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.
        </item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist
            John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen
            in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle
            starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a
            way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.
        </item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small
            Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place
            in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him,
            she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.
        </item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent
            with ties to his family\'s past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.
        </item>
        <item>A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool\'s PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2
            as a Princess Bride-esque story that\'s full of magic, wonder zero F\'s.
        </item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’
            discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at
            home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make
            impossible decisions to save their kind.
        </item>
        <item>As Goku investigates the destruction of the Southern Galaxy, Vegeta is taken to be
            King of the New Planet Vegeta, and to destroy the Legendary Super Saiyan, Broly.
        </item>
        <item>In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his
            supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four
            personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an
            orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.
        </item>
        <item>Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d\'état is taking place in
            Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.
        </item>
        <item>Many thousands of years in the future, Earth’s cities roam the globe on huge wheels,
            devouring each other in a struggle for ever diminishing resources. On one of these
            massive traction cities, the old London, Tom Natsworthy has an unexpected encounter with
            a mysterious young woman from the wastelands who will change the course of his life
            forever.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_movie_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mortalengine</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_tvshows_name">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Game Of Thrones</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Grey Anatomi</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_tvshows_date">
        <item>October 10, 2012</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>February 26, 1986</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>October 7, 2014</item>
        <item>April 17, 2011</item>
        <item>September 22, 2014</item>
        <item>March 27, 2005</item>
        <item>March 28, 2019</item>
    </array>
    <array name="data_tvshows_score">
        <item>Score : 75%</item>
        <item>Score : 62%</item>
        <item>Score : 70%</item>
        <item>Score : 64%</item>
        <item>Score : 65%</item>
        <item>Score : 67%</item>
        <item>Score : 81%</item>
        <item>Score : 68%</item>
        <item>Score : 63%</item>
        <item>Score : 64%</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_tvshows_overview">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht
            is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the
            city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.
        </item>
        <item>The Doom Patrols members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman
            abilities — but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden, the
            team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate the
            weirdest phenomena in existence and to protect Earth from what they find.
        </item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy
            whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The
            young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a
            teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the dragon balls brought her to Gokus home.
            Together, they set off to find all seven dragon balls in an adventure.
        </item>
        <item>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting
            Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of
            transportation. But Natsu isnt just any ordinary kid, hes a member of one of the worlds
            most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.
        </item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin Sweet animated series featuring the
            adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois
            have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and
            taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and
            Chris (the middle kid, hes not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final
            member of the family is Brian a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in
            check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
        </item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is
            struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of
            super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen
            guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to
            discover he is not the only meta-human who was created in the wake of the accelerator
            explosion and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with
            S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close
            friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it wont
            be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become...The Flash.
        </item>
        <item>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction
            between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the
            farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Nights Watch,
            is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.
        </item>
        <item>Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM. Everyone knows the name Commissioner
            Gordon. He is one of the crime worlds greatest foes, a man whose reputation is
            synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordons story and his rise from
            rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the multiple
            layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the worlds
            most iconic villains? And what circumstances created them the larger-than-life personas
            who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?
        </item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattles Grey
            Sloan Memorial Hospital.
        </item>
        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young
            girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth
            the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_tvshows_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
    </array>
</resources>
